《地球百子》前情提要
Previously on "The 100"...
我是最後一名夜之血脈
I am the last Natblida,
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
■
僅供學習 禁止用於任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.ZiMuZu.tv
初代赫達貝卡的繼承人
heir to Bekka pramheda.
你們都將向我臣服
And you are my subjects.
翻譯  七七  菲力  大嘴
■
我們需要增加光之城的人口
We need to increase the population in the City of Light.
校對  喃喃
更多人的人加入這項任務
The more minds turned to the task,
阿莉就會更加強大
the more powerful ALIE becomes
亞哈給所有人都吃了芯片
Jaha has been chipping everyone.
時間軸  姜姜  三水
賈斯珀說的是真的  我親眼所見
Jasper's right. I've seen it with my own eyes.
如今方舟已不復存在
Now that Arkadia has fallen,
後期  寶寶
我們將繼續第二階段
we'll move on to stage two.
你在幹什麼  住手
What are you doing? Stop!
總監  阿飄
打開微信   掃瞄左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    美劇炸了
瞭解最新影視資訊字幕信息
雷文
Raven...
你知道的太多了  我不能讓他們得到你
You know too much. I can't let them have you.
雷文
Raven...
阿莉為什麼要你自殺
Why did Alie want you to kill yourself?
因為我知道為什麼她要找到人工智能第二代
Because I know why she wants the second A.I.
為什麼
Why?
那是唯一能阻止她的東西
It's the only thing that can stop her.
你聽說過對阿爾法站進行的
You ever hear the one about the massacre
那次大屠殺嗎
on Alpha Station?
-沒  -沒聽過
-No. -No?
-沒  -你呢
-No. -You?
聽我說
Well, listen.
那是在聯合日後不久
It--it wasn't long after Unity Day, right?
第一代人  他們不知道
Generation one, they didn't know
他們再也回不來地球了
that they were leaving the ground forever.
有些人失去了理智
Some of them lost their minds.
我不想聽
Not listening.
六小時後我們就要和其他人匯合
We got to meet the others in 6 hours.
我要睡覺
I need sleep.
他討厭鬼故事
Oh, he hates ghost stories.
我想聽
Well, I want to hear it,
講吧  米勒  嚇嚇我
So come on, Miller. Scare me.
好吧
All right.
有一個人
There's this one guy...
是巴西人  他叫菲達爾戈船長
Brazilian, Captain Fidalgo. That was his name.
他開始在夢裡
He started to see his dead wife
看到他死去的妻子和孩子
and kids in his dreams.
他們都是被炸彈炸死的
They were all burned up from the bombs.
他告訴船上的醫生
He told the ship's doc
他們看起來像惡魔
that they looked like demons.
過了不久
After a while,
他連醒著的時候都會看到他們
he started to see them when he was awake, too.
他不停乞求他們住手
He would beg and beg and beg them
求他們放過他
to leave him alone, just to stop, right?
他們說只有他做一件事
They said the only way they'd leave him alone
他們才會放過他
was if he did one thing.
什麼事
What?
殺戮
Kill.
像惡魔一樣
Well, like demons do.
沒錯  像惡魔一樣
Yeah. Like demons do.
他選了金屬鉤來當武器
His weapon of choice-- metal hook.
一個鉤子
A hook?
你就這點能耐嗎
That's the best you can do?
閉嘴  布萊恩  讓他講完
Shut up, Bryan. Let him tell it.
他一夜就殺了十一個人
So he murdered 11 people in one night.
他掏出他們的內臟  胡亂掛起來
He gutted them and strung them up in the mess.
最可怕的是  當警衛發現他時
Worst part of it, when the guards found him,
他也被切成了碎片
He was cut into pieces, too.
他用自己的血和未被砍斷的胳膊
He wrote a single word with his own blood on the floor
在地板上寫下了一個詞  "惡魔"
with the arm that he didn't hack off --"Demons."
天啊  我討厭你
God, I hate you.
你們知道
Anyway, you know that,
我們在阿爾法站不時會聽到的摩擦聲嗎
that scraping sound we hear at Alpha Station sometimes?
有人說那是菲達爾戈的鬼魂
Some say that's Fidalgo's ghost
拖著他的金屬鉤劃過墻
dragging his metal hook along the walls,
乞求惡魔住手的聲音
begging the demons to stop,
但他們從未住手
but they never do,
如今他又回來了
and he's back
尋找他的下一個受害者
looking for his next victim!
我內急
Anyway, uh, nature calls.
留神聽聽鉤子聲
Listen for that hook, right?
別怕  布萊恩
Look. Relax, Bryan.
外面沒有惡魔  只有沒聽到
No demons out there, just Grounders
解除封鎖的地表人
who didn't hear the blockade was lifted.
還有吞下了芯片的方舟大軍
Army of chipped Arkadians.
看我幹什麼  他是你男朋友
Don't look at me. He's your boyfriend.
好吧
Oh, yeah.
讓我男朋友見鬼去吧
Kick my boyfriend's ass.
祝你好運
Good luck.
要是你們找到菲達爾戈船長
Hey, when you guys find Captain Fidalgo,
讓他幫忙多砍點柴火好嗎
get him to chop up some more firewood, ok?
天啊  演得真賣力  米勒
Oh, seriously, "A" for effort, Miller.
夥計們
Guys?
布萊恩
Bryan.
這已經不好玩了
Guys, this isn't funny anymore.
米勒
Miller.
你們嚇到我了
Got me.
開心了吧  你們現在可以回來了
You're hilarious. You can come back now.
《地球百子》
第三季  第十二集
HDTV720轉WEB版個人調軸微修：字幕雷哥
赫達
He--heda.
-赫達  -敬赫達
- Heda. - For heda.
赫達
Heda!
Heda.
陌生人  想嘗一口嗎
Hey, stranger, care for a bite?
艾默莉  你在這做什麼
Emori, what the hell are you doing here?
烤老鼠
Cooking rats.
原來的小販在路上被殘忍地襲擊了
The old vendor was brutally attacked on the road.
外面太危險了
It's dangerous out there.
對  顯然如此
Yeah. Clearly, it is.
自從你被抓
I have been looking for you
我就一直在找你
ever since you were taken,
然後我聽說新任赫達身邊
and then I heard rumors of the new heda's
有個英俊的天空人火種守護者
handsome skaikru flame keeper.
我就知道一定是你
I knew it had to be you.
我把你教得很好
I taught you well.
這個目標選得好  約翰
She's one hell of a mark, John.
加我一個
I want in.
今天新抓的老鼠  先生
我要一隻  謝謝
Uh, love one. Thank you.
真好吃
Mm, it's the best.
這是我吃過的最好吃的老鼠了
It's the best rat I've ever had.
不許再掉隊
Do not fall behind again.
這條街往下走
Keep following this street,
左手邊的小巷裡  走到一半有扇黑色的門
alley on the left, black door halfway down.
我一有機會就脫身
I'll get away as soon as I can.
貝卡的日記太精彩了
Becca's journal is amazing.
26歲時  她找到了連通人腦的方法
At 26, she found a pathway to access a human mind.
同年  她不得不把阿莉鎖起來
That same year, she had to lock up Alie
因為她認為這個世界的問題
because her answer for what was wrong
在於人口太多
with the world was too many people.
她27歲時  阿莉發射了炸彈
She was 27 when it launched the bombs.
關於火種  她寫了什麼
What did she write about the flame?
阿莉二代
Alie 2.0.
她認為這是她贖罪的辦法
She saw it as a way to atone for her sins.
她將它設計成不只是連通人腦
She designed it to not just access a human mind,
而是與它融為一體
but to merge with one.
它不會屠殺人類  因為它會成為我們的一員
It could never wipe us out because it would be one of us.
她首先把它放在了自己身上
She would put it in herself first,
改變基因讓自己的身體不會排斥植入
altered her genes so her body wouldn't reject the implant.
初代赫達貝卡  第一任指揮官
Bekka Pramheda, the first Commander.
基因改造讓她的血變成了黑色  對嗎
The gene therapy made her blood black, didn't it?
-沒錯  -你怎麼知道的
-Yeah. -How did you know that?
夜之血脈
Nightblood.
這就是它的起源
That's where it came from.
不知為何它變成了可遺傳的基因
Somehow it became hereditary.
露娜就有
Luna has it.
所以我們必須要找到她
That's why we have to find her.
如果她能植入阿莉二代
If she can access Alie 2...
她就能告訴我們如何阻止阿莉一代
She can tell us how to stop Alie 1.
初代赫達貝卡
Bekka Pramheda gets
得到了贖罪的機會
her second shot at atonement.
回到連通大腦那段
Get back to the mind pathway.
如果阿莉用它把我們的大腦
If Alie uses it to upload our minds
上傳到光之城
to the City of Light,
那我媽媽就有可能還活著
Then there's a chance my mom's still alive.
那得看你怎麼定義"活著"了
That depends on your definition of "alive."
瞪大眼睛  備好武器
Eyes sharp. Weapons hot.
我們就要到了
We're almost home.
米勒  請回答
Miller, come in.
哈珀  你在嗎
Harper, you there?
我們還有兩分鐘就到了
Ride's two minutes out.
真是個好頭
Good start.
方舟領地
我們兩天前就離開了
We left two days ago.
為什麼他們還沒修好大門
Why haven't they fixed the gate?
也許因為根本沒人會來修了
Maybe because there's no one here to fix it.
這就像座鬼城
It's like a ghost town.
米勒  你到底在哪兒
Miller, where the hell are you?
我不喜歡這樣
I don't like this.
也許他們也吞了芯片
Maybe they got chipped.
如果他們吞了芯片
If they got chipped,
他們會在洞穴那等著我們
they'd have been waiting for us at the cave.
也許他們看到門開著
Maybe they saw the open gate,
就進去拿林肯的書了
went in for Lincoln's book.
也許你能不要再說"也許"了
Maybe you should stop saying "maybe."
如果他們吞了芯片
If they are chipped,
那阿莉已經知道我們要來了
Alie already knows we're coming.
我們快去拿了書走吧
Let's get his book and get the hell out of here.
這方案我贊同
That's a plan I can support.
林肯
Lincoln.
關上門  把車掉個頭
Close it up. Turn the rover around.
我們也許會需要迅速離開
We may need to get out of here quickly.
看起來他們起身就走了
Looks like they just got up and walked away.
我們得快點
We're in and out.
打包儘可能多的工具放進車裡
Pack as much gear as you can into the rover.
我去拿地圖
I'll get the map.
我和她一起去  不能有人落單
I'll, uh, go with her. No one should be alone.
你不想打包是嗎
You don't want to load gear, huh?
一點也不想
Not even a little.
著什麼急  他們不會回來的
What's the rush? They won't be coming back.
你怎麼知道
How do you know?
阿莉的任務是讓大家都吞下芯片
Alie's mission is to chip everyone.
她沒理由再回一個已經佔領了的地方
It wouldn't make sense to return to a place she already took.
要是她知道有個去過光之城的人  你
Might make sense if there were someone in that place...
會告訴我們這些事  她就有理由回來了
I.E., you--who could tell us stuff like that.
有道理  我們快打包工具吧
Good point. Let's load gear.
怎麼了
What?
還記得你對我說一切都會好起來嗎
Remember when you told me it--it gets better?
這是兩碼事
This is not the same thing.
你崩潰一下也沒關係的  奧克塔維亞
You know, it's ok to fall apart a little, Octavia.
你愛他
You loved him.
戰爭結束之前
A warrior doesn't mourn the dead
戰士是不會哀悼亡者的
until the war is over.
我在走廊等你
I'll wait in the hall.
露娜  我們來了
Luna, we're on our way.
地表人
Grounder.
賈斯帕
Jasper...
準備好向我證明你有多想我了嗎
Ready to prove how much you miss me?
我認得其中幾種技術
I recognize some of this tech.
我猜猜
Oh, let me guess.
火種守護者也曾是你的顧客嗎
Flame keeper was one of your customers?
她是誰
Who is this?
人稱初代赫達貝卡
They, uh, call her Bekka Pramheda.
她是第一代司令
She was the first Commander.
貝卡
Becca.
拜託  別告訴我你真
Come on. Don't tell me you actually
信仰這種東西
believe in this religious crap.
尋求更高的東西
你確定沒人會來嗎
Are you sure no one will come in?
我看著像確定的樣子嗎
Does it seem like I'm sure?
大家都結一下手頭的事
Everyone finish what you're doing.
來軍械庫和我匯合
Meet me at the armory.
為什麼  怎麼了
Why? What's going on?
你們過來就知道了
You'll see when you get here.
-我們走運了  -這就去
- We just got lucky. - On our way.
等一下  把阿莉二代留下
Wait. Leave Alie 2.
為什麼
Why?
我好像知道怎麼激活它了
I think I know how to activate it.
不需要夜之血脈嗎
Without a nightblood?
這個部分寫的是用於激活的
This section here codes for activation
口令代碼
using a spoken passphrase.
你能讀懂嗎
You can read that?
不  你怎麼讀懂的
That's-- no. How?
這與我們使用的語言完全不同
None of our systems are in this language,
而你是笨程序員
and you're a lousy coder.
給
Here.
什麼口令
What phrase?
上面沒說  什麼都有可能
It's doesn't say. It could be anything.
它曾在萊克薩體內  她應該知道
It was in Lexa, right? She would've known it.
萊克薩連自己是人工智能都不知道
Lexa didn't even know she was an A.I.
她不是人工智能
She wasn't an A.I.
只是被人工智能強化了思維而已
Her mind was just enhanced by one.
她不知道的原因應該是
I'm guessing the reason she didn't know
程序隨著時間的推移退化了
was because the program degraded over time.
丟失了部分代碼
Parts of it got lost.
好好想想  克拉克
Think, Clarke.
口令有可能是對萊克薩意義非凡的一段話
It might have been a phrase that meant something to Lexa,
她不斷重複的話
words she said over and over again.
血債就要血償
"Blood must have blood."
血債血償
"Jus drein jus daun."
尋求更高的東西
"Seek higher things."
等等
Wait.
貝卡的書裡凈是些拉丁語
Becca's book is full of Latin phrases.
阿莉應該沒讓你學會拉丁語吧
I take it Alie didn't leave Latin behind in your brain.
我學過點拉丁語
I studied some Latin.
尋求更高的東西
"Seek higher things."
尋求更高
"Altiora...petimus."
不對  我再試試意譯
No. Go for less literal translation.
勇往
"Ascende...
直前
superius."
怎麼回事
What happened?
勇往直前
Ascenda superius.
別
Oh, hey, no.
它好像能感知到你的思想
It's like it sensed your mind.
火種到了沒有夜之血脈的人身上
When someone without the blood takes the flame,
會害死他們
the flame takes their life.
好吧  那肯定還有別的辦法
Ok. There must be another way
獲得代碼
to access the code, then.
沒別的辦法
There's not.
在找到宿主之前
Until we find it a host,
我們無法知道如何阻止阿莉
we won't know how to stop Alie.
那我們就找個宿主
Then let's find it a host.
走吧  貝拉米等著呢
Come on. Bellamy's waiting,
還有露娜
And so's Luna.
我們隨後就到
Ok. We'll catch up.
你還知道哪些別人沒教過你的東西
So what else do you know that no one ever taught you?
只要我們找到露娜  這一切就結束了
Once we find Luna, this will all be over.
安塔麗的假司令身份會曝光
Ontari'll be exposed as a fraud,
人工智能會告訴我們如何阻止阿莉
and the A.I. will tell us how to shut down Alie.
如果我們阻止了阿莉
If we shut down Alie,
光之城會怎麼樣
what happens to the City of Light?
你媽媽會像雷文一樣清醒過來
Your mom will come back like Raven did.
我媽媽呢
What about mine?
有人在這裡
Someone's here.
跟著怪異音樂可不是好主意
Following the creepy music is a bad idea.
或者我們也可以跟著走
Or we can follow the creepy music.
阿倫
"Aaron."
我有不好的預感  我們走吧
I don't like this. We should go.
瓦斯  快跑
Gas. Run!
-克拉克  -貝拉米
- Clarke... - Bellamy...
克拉克  怎麼了
Clarke, oh, what is it?
出什麼事了
What's going on?
是埃莫森
Emerson.
艾默莉  你得離開波利斯
Emori, you got to leave Polis, all right?
你在這裡不安全
Hey, it's not safe for you here.
我能照顧好自己
I can look after myself.
你到底是怎麼飛黃騰達的
Now, how the hell did you pull this off?
你瞭解我
Well, you know me.
不過是想活下去而已
Just doing what I can to stay alive, right?
你謙虛的時候真可愛
You're cute when you're modest.
不過我是認真的
I'm being serious, though.
安塔麗很瘋狂  連我都這麼覺得
Ontari, she's crazy, and that's coming from me.
我還活著只是因為
The only reason why I'm still breathing,
她以為我知道怎麼讓她當上司令
she thinks I know how to make her the Commander.
她不已經是司令了嗎
I thought she was the Commander.
嚴格來說  還不是
Not technically. No.
要當司令  你得往腦袋裡
To be the Commander, you have to shove
塞個電腦芯片
a computer chip into your brain.
那幫傻子以為那是輪迴轉世
These fools think it's reincarnation.
你憑什麼覺得你能幫她
Why would you think you could do this?
因為我親眼看著芯片從上任司令身上取出來
Because I saw it come out of the last Commander.
別問了
Don't ask.
那你現在為她做什麼
So what do you do for her now?
她喜歡我
She's taken a liking to me.
這可不怪她
Who could blame her?
快走
Go.
什麼事
What?
赫達要見你  火種守護者
Heda requires your presence, flame keeper.
當然了  謝謝
Of course she does. Thank you.
你還挺重要
So important.
我得走了
I got to go.
你留在這裡  這裡很安全
Stay here, ok? You'll be safe.
蒙蒂呢
Where's Monty?
被埃莫森抓走了
Emerson took him.
為什麼
Why?
奧克塔維亞  能聽見嗎  回話
Octavia, can you hear me? Come in.
賈斯帕和她在一起
Jasper was with her.
賈斯帕  你在嗎  說句話
Jasper, are you there? Say something.
米勒  哈珀  布萊恩
Miller, Harper, Bryan.
都是我的錯
This is all my fault.
我饒了埃莫森一命
I let Emerson live.
你在說什麼
What are you talking about?
在波利斯  我曾有機會處死他
In Polis, I had a chance to kill him,
可我放了他
and I let him go.
貝拉米  怎麼了
Bellamy, what's wrong?
雷文  你們沒事吧  你們在哪
Raven, are you ok? Where are you?
還在工程室  我們沒事
Still in engineering. We're fine.
雷文  聽我說
Raven, listen to me.
埃莫森在這裡  其他人和你在一起嗎
Emerson is here. Are the others with you?
沒有  這裡只有辛克萊
Negative. Just Sinclair.
韋瑟山的埃莫森
Mount Weather Emerson?
對  封鎖機艙
Yes. Ok. Lock down the hangar bay.
除了我們別讓任何人進去
Don't let anyone in but us.
你待在這裡  我來鎖門
Stay here. I'll lock the doors.
這個埃莫森吞過芯片嗎
Is this guy Emerson chipped?
昨天之前沒有
He wasn't as of yesterday.
他想復仇
He wants revenge.
雷文
Raven.
他在這裡  他在機艙裡
He's here. He's inside the hangar bay.
雷文  我來了
Raven, I'm coming.
打開機艙門
Open the hangar door! Ah!
他切斷了電源  手動開
He cut the power, so do it manually.
-雷文  -雷文
- Raven! - Raven!
外門
The outer door.
雷文  回到車上去  鎖上車門
Raven, get back in the rover! Lock the door!
不
No.
不  不  待在車裡
No, no, no, no. Please stay in the rover.
待在車裡
Stay in the rover, please.
Stay in the rover.
待在車裡
Stay--stay in the rover.
我會救你出去的
I'm gonna get you out of here.
不  沒事  沒事
No. Uh--agh. It's ok. It's ok.
沒事  待在車裡
It's ok. Stay in the rover.
待在車裡
Stay in the rover.
你快回車上去
Just go back, please.
快回去  回去
Please go back. Go back.
我會救你出去的
I'm gonna get you out of here.
不  待在車裡
No, no. Stay-- stay in the rover.
待在車裡  待在車裡
Stay in the rover. Stay in the rover.
待在...
Stay...
雷文  辛克萊
Raven. Sinclair.
雷文  跟著我
Raven. After me.
辛克萊
Sinclair.
我們來晚了
We're too late.
不  我們沒有
No, we're not.
他沒有殺蒙蒂和雷文
He didn't kill Monty or Raven.
不然他會丟下他們的屍體的
He would have left their bodies.
他把他們帶去了別的地方
He took them somewhere.
如果你是對的
If you're right, Octavia
奧克塔維亞和其他人也在那裡
and the others are there, too.
他會把他們帶去哪裡呢
Where would he be taking them?
他們可能在任何地方
They could be anywhere.
他熟悉這裡的構造嗎
Does he even know his way around?
他之前在這裡
He was here.
而你在韋瑟山
You were in Mount Weather.
氣閘艙
The airlock.
埃莫森  我知道你在聽
Emerson, I know you're listening.
我們得談談
We need to talk.
我什麼都不必做
I don't need to do anything.
你該抓住機會殺了我的
You should've killed me when you had the chance.
現在你來殺我了  是嗎
And now you're here to kill me. Is that it?
差不多吧
Something like that.
那就放了我的朋友
Then let my friends go.
放了他們  換我
Do that, and you can have me.
你很勇敢  克拉克
You're brave, Clarke.
克拉克
Clarke...
我讚賞你這點
I'll give you that.
我知道自己在做什麼
I know what I'm doing.
他們很幸運能有你這個朋友
They're lucky to have a friend like you.
立刻來氣閘艙
Come to the airlock,
不許帶武器
no weapons, right now.
給
Here.
你要做什麼
What the hell are you doing?
救他們
Saving them.
這事結束之後  帶著這個去找露娜
Look. When it's over, take this to Luna.
雷文知道該怎麼辦
Raven'll know what to do with it.
答應我
Promise me.
不
No.
你要是覺得我會讓你自己去面對
You're out of your mind
那你就錯了
if you think I'm letting you do this alone.
貝拉米  這是我的錯
Bellamy, this is my fault.
我不會讓任何人為我的錯誤買單
I'm not letting anyone else die for my mistake.
你就拿著吧
Ok, so take it.
你說完了嗎
You through?
我不知道在波利斯
I don't know what happened
你和埃莫森之間發生了什麼
between you and Emerson in Polis,
但我知道今天讓他
But I do know that letting him
在這殺了你是個很愚蠢的計畫
kill you here today is a stupid plan.
你還有更好的計畫嗎
You got a better one?
分散他的注意力  我會殺了他
Distract him. I shoot him.
司令的決定已下
Commander's decision is final.
-謝謝  -謝謝  赫達
- Thank you. - Thank you, Heda.
你是下一個  快
You're next. Come on.
上前
Step forward.
說吧  你想要什麼
只想給你你所需要的東西
Only to give you what you need.
你個混蛋
You son of a bitch.
你好  約翰
Hello, John.
看來你自己過得不錯啊
You've done well for yourself, I see.
他是誰
Who is this?
你的火種守護者是我的老朋友
Your flame keeper and I are old friends.
朋友
Friends.
我不知道
You know, I don't know what
你來這做什麼  亞哈
you're doing here, Jaha,
但要是我是你
but if I were you, I'd leave
我會抓住機會離開
while I still can.
你不必做一個假司令
You don't have to be a false Commander.
都出去
你是怎麼知道的
How do you know that?
你告訴我的
You told me...
他在撒謊
He's lying.
顯然  你該殺了他
Obviously, you should kill him right now
因為他污衊你
for insulting you.
就像你告訴了我
Just as you told me you would be unable
即使你有火種
to perform the ascension ritual,
你也不會進行繼任儀式
even if you had the flame.
是你
It was you?
你吞了芯片
You took the chip.
她是市場上那個女孩
This is the girl from the market.
你當時表現得根本不認識她一樣
You acted as if you didn't know her.
我是他的情人
I'm his lover.
是嗎
Really?
安塔麗  聽我說
Ontari, listen to me.
你不能相信他們
You cannot trust these people.
看來我不能相信的只有你
Seems the only person I can't trust is you.
我告訴過你背叛我的後果
I told you what would happen if you betrayed me.
你殺了他
You kill him,
我就不幫你了
I won't help you.
為什麼
Why?
他是個騙子  但他知道一些
He's a fraud, but he does have knowledge
對我們都有用的信息
that could be useful to all of us.
相信我
Trust me.
抓住這個騙子
安塔麗  聽我說
Ontari, listen to me, ok?
這人嘴裡沒一句真話
Nothing this man says is the truth, ok?
你不能相信...放開我
You can't believe... Let go of me.
亞哈  聽我說
Jaha! Listen to me.
安塔麗  什麼都別相信
Ontari, you can't believe anything...
什麼都別吃
Don't take anything...
不  不
No! No!
你在執政
You're ruling
但你卻沒得到司令的靈魂指引
without the wisdom of the Commander's spirit.
你的子民很快會發現的
Your people will soon figure that out.
我可以給你
I can offer you something
比火種更加強大的東西
even more powerful than the flame...
初代赫達貝卡的真正遺產
True legacy of Bekka Pramheda,
所有的力量  智慧
All power, all wisdom
都匯聚在一個小鑰匙裡
contained in one simple key.
你只需吞下它
All you have to do is swallow it.
我完成了我的承諾
I held up my part of the deal.
該你了
Your turn.
放我朋友走
Let my friends go.
先讓貝拉米現身
Tell Bellamy to show himself first.
我不知道你在說...
I don't know what you're talk...
不
No.
好
Good.
掏出彈夾  扔到走廊盡頭
Now take out the clip. Throw it down the hall.
把槍放在地上
Put the gun on the ground
進來
and get inside.
拜託  你想要抓的是我
Please. You wanted me.
只要你放了他們  我就進去
I'll get inside once you let them go.
我在跟貝拉米說話
I was talking to Bellamy.
好  好  住手
Ok, ok. Just--just stop.
貝拉米  不要
Bellamy, don't.
那是給你準備的
Those are yours.
跪下  克拉克
Get on your knees, Clarke.
把手放在頭後面
Put your hands behind your head.
不
No.
你想怎麼處置我都可以  好嗎
You can do anything you want with me, ok?
就讓他們走吧
Just let them go.
你殺害了381個人
You murdered 381 people.
你奪走了我的孩子
You took the lives of my children,
兄弟  朋友
my brother, my friends.
你真的以為我殺了你
Did you really think that I would be happy
就能滿足了嗎
with just one life in return, hmm?
五號氣閘艙  排出氧氣
Airlock 5, oxygen venting.
現在你能感受到我當時的痛苦了
Now you're gonna feel what I felt.
求我住手啊
Beg me to stop it.
我讓你求我
I told you to beg!
-求求你  -大點聲
- I'm begging you. - Louder!
求你了
Please!
貝拉米
Bellamy...
阿倫不會希望你做這種事的
Aaron wouldn't want you to do this.
你不許提他的名字
You don't say his name!
不
No...
還沒完
Not yet.
首先  你要親眼看著他們死
First, you'll watch them die.
你有什麼想對你的朋友說的嗎
You have any last words for your friends?
有
Yeah.
勇往直前
Ascende superius.
什麼
What...
不
Oh! No.
No.
願我們早日重逢
May we meet again.
你的戰鬥結束了
該走了  我去拿地圖
It's time to go. I'll get the map.
我們要走了  你們怎麼還沒準備好
Hey, we're leaving. Why aren't you ready?
我們不和你們走了
We're not going with you.
雷文
Raven...
他幾乎走不了路  我的肩膀痛得要死
He can barely walk, and my shoulder's killing me.
但我的頭腦還非常好使
My brain's all kinds of awesome.
她想起阿莉把自己下載到了
She remembered that Alie downloaded herself
方舟的主機上
into the Ark mainframe.
如果代碼還在主機上
If the code is still there,
我們或許能發現個後門
we might be able to find a back door.
我猜一旦你將阿莉二代
I'm guessing once you connect Alie 2
和露娜連通  我們就要連接阿莉一代
to Luna, we'll need to access Alie 1
來阻止她
to take her down.
米勒
Miller.
我們會保護他們的安全
We'll keep them safe.
我也要保護他們
I'll keep them safe.
那你呢  這裡會很危險的
How about you? It's gonna be dangerous.
你真瞭解我  我也加入
You know me well. I'm in.
好吧
Ok.
波利斯之門已經打開
The gates to Polis are open.
謝謝  艾默莉
Thank you, Emori.
是時候充實光之城了
It's time to fill the City of Light.
■
人人留學【免費辦理】
震撼上線，趕快登陸
www.rrliuxue.com
英、澳、日三國免費辦理
眾多美國大學，快捷錄取
■
人人留學——開啟單向收費新時代